Nothing is more sorrowful than dawn.
I should have slept without delay, but…
The night grew late;
Ah, I watched the moon until it sank low.
I should have slept without delay, but…
The night grew late;
Ah, I watched the moon until it sank low.
The last time, when
My sleep was not troubled by thoughts
Your hands through my hair
Comforted me
I’m left only to wonder
To gaze endlessly at the moon
All that’s left is to wish
For your gaze beyond the moon
In the dark night
In the dark night, night
It feels as though I don’t exist
That I have vanished
To everyone now, I’m a missing person
I have vanished
It feels as though I don’t exist
That I have vanished
To everyone now, I’m a missing person
The last time, when
My sleep was not troubled by thoughts
Your hands through my hair
Comforted me
I’m left only to wonder
To gaze endlessly at the moon
All that’s left is to wish
For your gaze beyond the moon
Nothing is more sorrowful than dawn.
In the dark night
In the dark night, night
Nothing is more sorrowful than dawn.